friendjungle.com 2009-02-07

# Friend Jungle

#### Definitions

The following discloses the Privacy Policy for the use of the website (herein referred to as the "Website", the "Service", "us", or "we") by you (herein referred to as "user", "member" or "you"). By using the Website in any way, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy, whether or not you register as a member to the Service. We may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. Notification of changes in this Privacy Policy will be posted on the Website or sent via electronic mail, as we may determine in our sole discretion. Your continued use of the Service will constitute a binding acceptance by you of this Privacy Policy, or any subsequent modifications.

#### Overview

As part of the normal operation of our services we collect information about you in order to offer the highest possibility of finding a partner through our site. As a matter of policy, we do not sell, rent, or give any personally identifiable information about you to any third party; **except for in cases where our terms and conditions may have been broken.**

#### Information you supply

If you have started, but not completed, the registration process, we may send you email messages encouraging you to complete the process and become a subscriber. Once you complete the registration process, we may also occasionally send you newsletters and email you notifications of special events or information on users that are establishing contact with you through our site. If you would rather not receive emails about new products, promotions or other noteworthy news, you may opt-out by visiting the "Settings" section. We further offer a subscriber-based service to users seeking partners. To process subscriptions we may require your name, billing address, phone number, email address and credit card information. Credit card transactions are processed through a third party billing company, which only uses your information for that purpose. In the event that we are acquired by another company, your personal information may be part of the assets transferred to the acquiring party. If this occurs, you will be notified if there are any material changes to the way your personally identifiable information is collected or used.

#### Information collected automatically

We automatically collect information, provided by your browser, when you visit our website. This information includes, but may not be limited to, your IP address, your browser, access times, the content of cookies we've previously set, and the referring website address. When you visit our website, we may assign your computer one or more cookies, to facilitate access to our site and to personalize your online experience. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, please note that you may not be able to sign in or use some of the interactive features offered on our website.

#### Use of your Information

We do not share your personal information with any third parties; **except for in cases where our terms and conditions may have been broken.** For our own purposes, however, we may make use of your information. These reasons may be, but are not limited to; resolving disputes, troubleshooting problems, enforcing our Terms and Conditions. These uses improve our Websites and help us better meet your needs as a user.

#### Disclosure

As a matter of policy, we do not sell, rent, or give any personally identifiable information about you to any third party; **except for in cases where our terms and conditions may have been broken.** All personally identifiable data is accessible solely to authorized employees, and they may do so only for permitted business functions. However, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed. By way of example (without limiting any of the foregoing), we may be required to disclose information to the government, law enforcement agencies or third parties. Under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or members may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from our Websites. Accordingly, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private. That being said, we want you to feel confident using our website. Users should also take care with how they handle and disclose their personal information and should avoid sending personal information through insecure email. Please refer to the United States Federal Trade Commission's website at http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/edu/microsites/idtheft/ for information about how to protect yourself against identity theft.

#### Your use of other Members' Information

Our services include access to instant messaging, and, while instant messaging another member, there may be specific contact information transmitted by one user to another. Under no circumstances may you disclose personally identifiable information about another member to any third party without our consent and the consent of such other member after adequate disclosure.

#### Age Restriction

You must be 18 years of age or over to register as a member of or be permitted use of the Website. Any information we receive from people we believe to be under the age of 18 will be purged from our database. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

#### Privacy of Information

There are regulations and laws that govern the way private sector organizations collects, uses, keeps, secures and discloses personal information. "Personal Information" means all information about an identifiable individual. We recognize the importance of privacy and the sensitivity of personal information received by us in the course of offering our service. Accordingly, we abide by the laws which govern this site, which include, but may not be limited to; Cyprus' Processing of Personal Data (Protection of the Individual) Law, and Directive 95/46/EC on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, Directive 2000/520/EC: Commission Decision of 26 July 2000 pursuant to Directive 95/46/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council, and Directive 2002/58/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council of 12 July 2002 concerning the processing of personal data and the protection of privacy in the electronic communications sector of the European Union.

#### Notice

We may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time based on changes in the law, our need to accurately reflect our data collection and disclosure practices, or your comments or suggestions. Notification of changes in this Agreement will be posted on the Website or sent via electronic mail, as we may determine in our sole discretion. If you object to anything in this Agreement or in the Privacy Statement, do not use the Website or the Service. Your continued use of the Service will constitute a binding acceptance by you of this Agreement, or any subsequent modifications.
